statsremote.com 2006-12-16

# StatsRemote :: Privacy Policy :: Your privacy is important to us.

Network 24/7 GmbH respects your privacy and personal sphere. 

**Collection and Processing of Personal Data**  
When you visit our Web sites, our Web server automatically records the name of your Internet service provider, the Web site from which you visit us, the Web sites you actually visit and the date and length of your visit. Additional personal data is only stored if volunteered by you, for example in the context of a registration or a survey.

**When using our software your personal login details and numbers of the supported affiliate programs and pay per click search engines are stored encrypted on your hard drive. We do not have access to your data at any time. Before StatsRemote checks your stats the software will connect to our server in order to check whether you are authorized to use the software. No information except the StatsRemote username and password is sent to our server at any time.**

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Data and Purpose Specification**  
Network 24/7 GmbH will use your personal data for the sole purpose of technical administration of the Web sites, customer fulfilment and administration, only to the extent necessary in each specific case. We will only disclose your data to governmental authorities in cases where it is required by law. Our employees are obliged by us to respect confidentiality.

**Freedom of Choice**  
We should like to use your data to inform you about our services and where applicable request your opinion. Naturally your participation is completely voluntary. Should you not consent, you can inform us at any time, so that we can specifically prohibit the use of your data accordingly. 

**Freedom of Information**  
Upon request, Network 24/7 GmbH will inform you, what personal data is stored by us as defined by local law. If such data is incorrect, we will correct that information at your request. 

**Security**  
Network 24/7 GmbH uses technical and organizational security measures in order to protect the data we have under our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or against access by unauthorized persons. Our security procedures are continually enhanced as new technology becomes available.

Should you have questions regarding data protection and privacy of your personal data, you can [contact us](mailto:info@network247.com?subject=StatsRemote%20Privacy%20Policy) any time.
